The Dictator Switch
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
We lost!
I refuse to accept this defeat!
We lost this match 'cuz of you!
Oh, really?
Don't "Oh, really" me!
Damn you, I'll beat you!
Damn it all!
Why only me?
It's because you suck in baseball.
Let's go out and practice so that this doesn't happen again.
But Giant's the problem!
Oh man! I wish he'd just vanish.
Hmm, you think so?
In that case, wanna try it out?
The Dictator Switch!
Dictator Switch?
It's the switch that was developed for the dictators in the 22nd century.
The term "Dictator" refers to the leader who...
...take political decisions and influence the world just by themselves.
The dictator gets rid of those who oppose him...
...as well as those who are an obstacle to him.
I didn't understand?
Making them non-existent.
Huh? The bee is gone!
See? You can get rid of anyone who's getting in your way.
Let's create a noble and just world!
But getting rid of people is terrifying thing to do.
I'll think over...
Sure, sure! Take your time.
Giant is a terrible boy, sure. But I do feel bad about getting rid of him.
The leftover from earlier.
Please help!
Be gone, Giant!
He vanished, indeed!
That was a terrible thing to do!
Why do you look so sad?
I... Giant...
But who's Giant, anyway?
Gouda Takeshi, a bully with fat belly!
Remember? He lives in our neighborhood!
What? Did such a boy exist, again?
You really don't know him?
Ah, right timing!
Teacher, please excuse us!
Gouda-kun? I don't have such a student in our class.
Never heard of him neither.
You can't be so serious.
You sure are a weird boy!
It seems when I get rid of people...
it becomes so that, they never existed to begin with.
We lost today's match 'cause of you!
Be gone, Suneo!
Oh my god! Suneo is gone!
It's not my fault!
I won't use it again on anyone. I'll return it to Doraemon.
We lost 'cuz of you!
Shut up or else, I'll get rid of you all!
Really!
Nobita, go and do your homework!
I request you to please not make me angry!
What? You want to return them back?
Impossible, it's not a toy!
No way...!
What a terrifying switch!
I get urge to use it!
Please stop!
Doraemon and you all, be gone!
It's eerily quiet here.
Mum! Doraemon!
There's nobody on road!
All must be out playing...
Shizuka-chan!
Doraemon!
Anybody home?
Hello!
Anyone home?
There's nobody besides me in this world! I've got rid of 'em all!
Oh no, I shouldn't have used it!
It's their fault!
There's no annoying mum or teacher!
I'll take what all I want!
I'm full!
It's boring to play games all alone.
I hate this!
Please come back all of you!
Please come back, Giant!
I'm feeling so lonely!
This is what happens when you get rid of people!
Did you understand now?
Yes, I did.
Doraemon!
Actually, this gadget was developed to condemn dictatorship.
Let's return them all back!
The loser's practicing baseball!
Do your best!
Bring it on!
He sure is a sucker, all right!
It's so much fun to play with annoying people!